{
    "id": "b5494566fe424c5d86ddf2c6447bd6d4",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I am waiting .......................... them.",
            "description": "wait + for",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't think that he will agree .............................. our suggestion.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "of",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We can't bank .................................. them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Whom does this bag belong ..............................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "of",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We walked right ................................ the desert.",
            "description": "Across is used to indicate movement in two dimensional spaces.",
            "answers": [
                "across",
                "over",
                "through"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She complained ………………………….. pain in her abdomen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "of",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Dad was upset when I failed ........................... my test.",
            "description": "fail + in",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I lent my bicycle ……………………………. him and never saw it again.",
            "description": "lent + direct object + to + indirect object",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven't heard anything .............................. him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He was robbed .............................. his belongings.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "off",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I can't agree ............................ this argument.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is quite good .............................. drawing.",
            "description": "We say good at.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}